Periscope UP063
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Periscope
1987 -- 2014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Human Resources
UP063
0.75 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Periscope which contains news and articles about human resources issues. The stories emphasize the human resouces aspects of working at Tufts.
Biographical / Historical
Department of Personnel: Started in 1966. First director was Viola Saltmarsh, former Director of Placement. Personnel functions prior to this department were under the purview of the Director of Placement and the Placement Office which was looks like a predecessor of Student Services/Career Counseling. The Department of Personnel changed its name to the Department of Human Resources in 1988 (or Human Resources Division per the Annual Report of the President to the Trustees, November 4, 1988)
- Periscope, 1987 -- 2014; UP063.001; 0.75 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Periscope which contains news and articles about human resources issues. The stories emphasize the human resouces aspects of working at Tufts.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Periscope, 1987; UP063.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Periscope, 1988; UP063.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Periscope, 1989; UP063.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Periscope, 1990; UP063.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Periscope, 1991; UP063.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Periscope, 1992; UP063.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Periscope, 1993; UP063.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Periscope, 1994; UP063.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Periscope, 1995; UP063.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Periscope, 1996 -- 1997; UP063.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 1998; UP063.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 1999; UP063.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2000; UP063.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2001; UP063.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2002; UP063.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2003; UP063.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2004; UP063.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2005-01; UP063.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2005-02; UP063.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2005-04; UP063.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2005-05; UP063.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2005-06; UP063.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2005-09; UP063.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2005-11; UP063.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2005-12; UP063.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2006-01; UP063.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2006-03; UP063.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
    No issue for Feb. published in 2006.
  - Periscope, 2006-04; UP063.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2006-05; UP063.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, Summer, 2006; UP063.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2006-09; UP063.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2006-10; UP063.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2006-11; UP063.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2006-12; UP063.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2007-01; UP063.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2007-02; UP063.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2007-03; UP063.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2007-04; UP063.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2007-05; UP063.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2007-06; UP063.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2007-07; UP063.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2007-09; UP063.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2007-11; UP063.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2008-01; UP063.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2008-03; UP063.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2008-05; UP063.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2008-07; UP063.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, Special Issue, 2008; UP063.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
    @Work Performance Development Program Celebrates 10 Years!
  - Periscope, 2008-09; UP063.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2008-11; UP063.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2009-01; UP063.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2009-03; UP063.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2009-05; UP063.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2009-07; UP063.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2009-09; UP063.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2009-11; UP063.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, 2010-01; UP063.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, March/April, 2010; UP063.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, May/June, 2010; UP063.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, July/August, 2010; UP063.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, September/October, 2010; UP063.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, November/December, 2010; UP063.001.002.00053 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, January/February, 2011; UP063.001.002.00054 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, March/April, 2011; UP063.001.002.00055 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, May/June, 2011; UP063.001.002.00056 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, July/August, 2011; UP063.001.002.00057 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, September/October, 2011; UP063.001.002.00058 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, November/December, 2011; UP063.001.002.00059 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, January/February, 2012; UP063.001.002.00060 (Box 2)
    newsletters
  - Periscope, March/April, 2012; UP063.001.002.00061 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, May/June, 2012; UP063.001.002.00062 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, July/August, 2012; UP063.001.002.00063 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, November/December, 2012; UP063.001.002.00064 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, January/February, 2013; UP063.001.002.00065 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, March/April, 2013; UP063.001.002.00066 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, May/June, 2013; UP063.001.002.00067 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, July/August, 2013; UP063.001.002.00068 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, September/October, 2013; UP063.001.002.00069 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, November/December, 2013; UP063.001.002.00070 (Box 2)
  - Periscope, January/February, 2014; UP063.001.002.00071 (Box 2)